Guide to the Stanford University, Provost's Office, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Office of Management and Budget, Series 4
  - Administrative structure: Project lnformation, Undated (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Administrative structure: Provost's Office, Undated (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Administrative structure: Public Events, Undated (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Revised allocation letter: cover sheet, etc, Undated (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Metteer WiII, Undated (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Parental loan plan, Undated (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Rosenberg, undated (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Lynden, Undated (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Tuition rate, Undated (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - SUNY-Binghamton Computer Center, Undated (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Stanford Center for Infomation Processing, Undated (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Aid Package Overlap brochure, Undated (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Factors affecting enrollment: decisions of admitted freshman applicants - Hopkins, Massy Curry, Undated (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - Interviews, Undated (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - A Survey of Admitted Stanford Applicants Who Accept and Decline Admission (John D. Back), Undated (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - Freshman admissions and Financial Aid: APO, 1973-1974, 1974-1975 (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - Master Plan for Publicly Funded Student Aid in California (from Bob Huff), Undated (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - Report on the Second Institutional Student Financial Aid Resources Survey for the fiscal years 1971-72 and 1972-73, Undated (Box 36, Folder 43)
  - Report to the Legislature on the College Opportunity Grant Program; inventory of student financial aid resources, Undated (Box 36, Folder 44)
  - Report on the University of California Educational Opportunity Program, 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 45)
  - Tuition rates, 1974-1975 (Box 36, Folder 46)
  - ATP report on college bound seniors, 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 47)
  - Commentary on 0'Hara Bill (received from Fennell Office), 1975 Jul 9 (Box 36, Folder 48)
  - The "Middle Income Problem": Hargadon/Massey response, Undated (Box 36, Folder 49)
  - Report of the ASSU Senate Select Committee on Tuition, Undated (Box 36, Folder 50)
  - Some Assorted Personal and Background Facts about Stanford Freshmen (back response by Bacchetti and Miller; press release by Zeyer), Undated (Box 36, Folder 51)
  - Federal Student Assistance: A Review of Title of the Higher Education Act, Undated (Box 36, Folder 52)
  - Admissions and Financial Aid, Undated (Box 36, Folder 53)
  - DAPER: Football coach search, Undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - DAPER: Women's Gymnastics coach search, Undated (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - DAPER: Golf coach search, Undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - DAPER: Basketball coach search, Undated (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - DAPER: ticket sales, Undated (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - DAPER: WOFAC, Undated (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - DAPER: club teams, Undated (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - DAPER: Intercollegiate Athletics, Undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Report on Intercollegiate Athletics at Stanford, Undated (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - DAPER: Dance program, Undated (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - DAPER: Football, Undated (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - DAPER: Golf, Undated (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - DAPER: Track, Undated (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - DAPER: salaries and classification, Undated (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - DAPER: internship position, Undated (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - DAPER: IRS and TV Coverage, Undated (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - DAPER: NCAA, Undated (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - DAPER: faculty reports, Undated (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - DAPER: fundraising, Undated (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - DAPER: gifts, Undated (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - DAPER program & board action: Hanna House breakfast - 4/25 8 a.m., Undated (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - DAPER: Student Athletic Council, Undated (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - CAPER, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - CAPER, 1977-1978 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - CAPER: meeting, 1976 Nov 1 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - CAPER: group meeting, 1978 Feb 21 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - DAPER: Title IX, Undated (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - DAPER: budget, 1975-1976 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - DAPER: budget, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - DAPER: budget, 1977-1978 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - DAPER: budget, 1978-1979 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - DAPER: budget - five year forecast, Undated (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - DAPER, 1978-1979 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - DAPER: hoId for EES meetings - Joe Ruetz, Undated (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - DAPER, 1975-1977 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - DAPER: Affirmative Action, Undated (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - DAPER: Berry Scholarship, Undated (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - DAPER: NORCAL, Undated (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - DAPER: Pow Wow, Undated (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - DAPER: scholarships, Undated (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - DAPER: Stanford Athletic Board, Undated (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - DAPER: assistant baseball coach search, Undated (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - DAPER: assistant basketball coach search, Undated (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - DAPER: Assistant Director of Sports Publicity Information, Undated (Box 37, Folder 44)
  - DAPER: assistant swimming coach search, Undated (Box 37, Folder 45)
  - DAPER: appointment policies, Undated (Box 37, Folder 46)
  - DAPER: appointments, Undated (Box 37, Folder 47)
  - DAPER: 12-unit PE activity courses limit, Undated (Box 37, Folder 48)
  - Budget: ARLO, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Budget: Admissions, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Budget: Business and Finance, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Budget: CRIS, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Budget: DAPER, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Budget: Dean of Student Affairs, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Budget: Dean of Student Affairs (Tresidder), 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Budget: Development, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Budget: Earth Sciences, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Budget: Education, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Budget: Engineering, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Budget: Engineering Incentive Plan, Undated (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Budget: Financial Aid - graduate, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Budget: Financial Aid - undergraduate, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Budget: Graduate School of Business, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Budget: Graduate Studies, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Budget: Hoover Institution, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Budget: Hospital, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Budget: Human Biology construction of, budget, 1976-1977 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Budget: Humanities and Sciences, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Budget: Independent Labs, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Budget: Law School, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Budget: Libraries, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Budget: Lots, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Budget: Medicine, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Budget: Memorial Church, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Budget: Overseas Studies, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Budget: President's/Provost's Office, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Budget: Press (University), 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Budget: Public Affairs, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Budget: Registrar's Office, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Budget: SCIP, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Budget: SLAC, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Budget: SSRL, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Budget: Student Health Service (Cowell), Undated (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Budget: Summer Session, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Budget: Summer Session, budget work·sheets, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - Budget: Undergraduate Studies, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - Budget: University Counsel, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - Budget: Values, Technology and Society (VTS), 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Budget: Operating Budget Guidelines, 1976-1977 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Budget: Operating Budget Guidelines, 1976-1977 (Box 39)
  - Budget: Operating Budget Guidelines, 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Budget: Operating Budget Guidelines, 1975-1976 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Budget: Protocols, 1976-1977 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Budget: Publicity, 1976-1977 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Budget: reports and papers, Parameters Papers, 1975-1976 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Budget: report and papers, "Taking Stock", 1976 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Budget: room and board rates, 1976-1977 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Budget: room and board rates, 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Budget: room and board rates, 1975-1976 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Budget: Tuition, 1975-1976 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Budget: year-end closing, 1975-1976 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Extraordinary salary increase, Undated (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Retirement: housing, Undated (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Residences for university officers, Undated (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - TIAA - CREF, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - TIAA - CREF, 1978- (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - TIAA - CREF, 1976-1977 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous: San Francisco Art Institute, Undated (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous: office technology, Undated (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous: cartoons and humor, Undated (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous: AIR Convention, 1979 May (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous: Griffin statues, Undated (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Personnel: faculty and staff housing, Undated (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Overseas Studies: contraction of office staff, Undated (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Committee on Foreign Study Programs: overseas studies appointments, Undated (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Committee on Foreign Study Programs, Undated (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Committee on Foreign Study Programs (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Berlin, Undated (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Berlin, Undated (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Cliveden, Undated (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Cliveden, Undated (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Florence, Undated (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - Florence, Undated (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Tours, Undated (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - Tours, Undated (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - Tours, Undated (Box 39, Folder 38)
  - Vienna, Undated (Box 39, Folder 39)
  - Vienna, Undated (Box 39, Folder 40)
  - WOFAC Co: Division of Science Management Corp., Undated (Box 39, Folder 41)
  - WACUBO: Business Management Institute, Undated (Box 39, Folder 42)
  - Title IX, Undated (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - Gifts, Undated (Box 39, Folder 44)
  - Administrative Panel on Safety and Health, Undated (Box 39, Folder 45)
  - Printing Services, Undated (Box 39, Folder 46)
  - Academic Council: Senate, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 47)
  - Academic Council: Advisory Board, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 48)
  - Academic programs: Exchange Programs, Undated (Box 39, Folder 49)
  - Academic programs: Graduate Studies, Undated (Box 39, Folder 50)
  - Academic programs: Overseas Studies, Undated (Box 39, Folder 51)
  - Academic programs: ROTC, Undated (Box 39, Folder 52)
  - Academic programs: Undergraduate Studies, Undated (Box 39, Folder 53)
  - Academic programs: University Progress Fund, Undated (Box 39, Folder 54)
  - Instructional units: Electrical Engineering, Undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Instructional units: Engineering-Economics System, Undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Instructional units: Industrial Engineering, Undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Instructional units: Materials Science, Undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Instructional units: Mechanical Engineering, Undated (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Instructional units: Operations Research, Undated (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Instructional units: Education, undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Instructional units: Earth Sciences, Undated (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Instructional units: Applied Earth Sciences, Undated (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Instructional units: Geology, Undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Instructional units: Geophysics, Undated (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Instructional units: Petroleum Engineering, Undated (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Instructional units: Graduate School of Business, Undated (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Instructional units: Electronics Research ?, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Instructional units: Engineering, Undated (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Instructional units: Aeronautics and Astronautics, Undated (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Instructional units: Applied Mechanics, Undated (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Instructional units: Chemical Engineering, Undated (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Instructional units: Civil Engineering, Undated (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Instructional units: Humanities and Sciences, Undated (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Instructional units: Anthropology, Undated (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Instructional units: Art, Undated (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Instructional units: Asian Languages, Undated (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Instructional units: Biological Sciences, Undated (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Instructional units: Chemistry, Undated (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Instructional units: Computer Sciences, Undated (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Instructional units: Comparative Literature, Undated (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Instructional units: French and Italian, Undated (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Instructional units: German Studies, Undated (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Instructional units: History, Undated (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Instructional units: Hopkins Marine Station, Undated (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Instructional units: Humanities Special Program, Undated (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Instructional units: Linguistics, Undated (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Instructional units: Mathematics, Undated (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Instructional units: Music, Undated (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Instructional units: Philosophy, Undated (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Instructional units: Physics, Undated (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Instructional units: Political Sciences, Undated (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Instructional units: Psychology, Undated (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Instructional units: Slavic Languages, Undated (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - Instructional units: Sociology, Undated (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - Instructional units: Spanish & Portuguese, Undated (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - Instructional units: Statistics, Undated (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - Instructional units: Undergraduate Specials, Undated (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - Instructional units: Communication, Undated (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - Instructional units: Classics, Undated (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - Instructional units: Drama, Undated (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - Instructional units: Economics, Undated (Box 40, Folder 48)
  - Instructional units: other, Undated (Box 40, Folder 49)
  - Instructional units: Fleischmann Laboratories, Undated (Box 40, Folder 50)
  - Instructional units: Food Research Institute, Undated (Box 40, Folder 51)
  - Instructional units: Hoover Institution, Undated (Box 40, Folder 52)
  - Instructional units: International Studies, Undated (Box 40, Folder 53)
  - Instructional units: Military Science, Undated (Box 40, Folder 54)
  - Instructional units: Physical Education & Athletics, Undated (Box 40, Folder 55)
  - Instructional units: Physical Education for Women, Undated (Box 40, Folder 56)
  - Instructional units: Physical Science, Undated (Box 40, Folder 57)
  - Instructional units: Stanford Linear Accelerator Center, Undated (Box 40, Folder 58)
  - Instructional units: Family, Community, and Preventitive Medicine, Undated (Box 40, Folder 59)
  - Instructional units: Genetics, Undated (Box 40, Folder 60)
  - Instructional units: Gynecology & Obstetrics, Undated (Box 40, Folder 61)
  - Instructional units: Medical Microbiology, Undated (Box 40, Folder 62)
  - Instructional units: Medical Medicine, Undated (Box 40, Folder 63)
  - Instructional units: Nursing, Undated (Box 40, Folder 64)
  - Instructional units: Pathology, Undated (Box 40, Folder 65)
  - Instructional units: Pediatrics, Undated (Box 40, Folder 66)
  - Instructional units: Pharmacology, Undated (Box 40, Folder 67)
  - Instructional units: Physical Therapy, Undated (Box 40, Folder 68)
  - Instructional units: Physiology, Undated (Box 40, Folder 69)
  - Instructional units: Psychiatry, Undated (Box 40, Folder 70)
  - Instructional units: Radiology, Undated (Box 40, Folder 71)
  - Instructional units: Surgery, Undated (Box 40, Folder 72)
  - Instructional units: Medicine, Undated (Box 40, Folder 73)
  - Instructional units: Anatomy, Undated (Box 40, Folder 74)
  - Instructional units: Anesthesia, Undated (Box 40, Folder 75)
  - Instructional units: Biochemistry, Undated (Box 40, Folder 76)
  - Instructional units: Dermatology, Undated (Box 40, Folder 77)
  - Dept. of Dermatology: Annual Report to the President, Academic Year, 1970-1971 (Box 40, Folder 78)
  - Instructional units: Law, Undated (Box 40, Folder 79)
  - Administrative structure: Tresidder Union, Undated (Box 40, Folder 80)
  - Administrative structure: University Relations, Undated (Box 40, Folder 81)
  - Administrative structure: Hopkins Marine Station, Undated (Box 40, Folder 82)
  - Administrative structure: GSO, Undated (Box 40, Folder 83)
  - Administrative structure: FinanciaI Aids, Undated (Box 40, Folder 84)
  - Administrative structure: Cowell Student Health Center, Undated (Box 40, Folder 85)
  - Administrative structure: Controller's Office, Undated (Box 40, Folder 86)
  - Administrative structure: Chapel, Undated (Box 40, Folder 87)
  - Administrative structure: Center for Research and Development in Higher Education, Undated (Box 40, Folder 88)
  - Administrative structure: Center for Inter-Disiplinary Research, Undated (Box 40, Folder 89)
  - Administrative structure: Career Planning and Placement, Undated (Box 40, Folder 90)
  - Career Planning and Placement Center annual report, 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 91)
  - Administrative structure: Business and Finance, Undated (Box 40, Folder 92)
  - Administrative structure: Board of Trustees, Undated (Box 40, Folder 93)
  - Administrative structure: ASSU, Undated (Box 40, Folder 94)
  - Administrative structure: Alumni Association, Undated (Box 40, Folder 95)
  - Administrative structure: Administrative Computing Facility, Undated (Box 40, Folder 96)
  - Administrative structure: Academic Information Center, Undated (Box 40, Folder 97)
  - Administrative structure: Academic Senate, Undated (Box 40, Folder 98)
  - Administrative structure: Academic Council, Undated (Box 40, Folder 99)
  - Administrative structure: Academic Calendar, Undated (Box 40, Folder 100)
  - 01 General, 1979- (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - 01 General Duena Gate/ Main Quad Gate, 1979- (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - 01-01 Administration, 1979- (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - 01-01 Humanities and Sciences, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - 01-01 Undergraduate Studies, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - 01-10 President's Office, 1979- (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - 01-20 Classics, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - 01-30 Afro-American Studies-Compar. Lot., 1979- (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - 01-40 English 1979- [1964-1972] (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - 01-50 English, 1979- (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - 01-60 Humanities Special Programs, 1974- (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - 01-70 Religious Studies 1968- (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - 01-90 Philosophy 1977 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - 01-100 Anthropology-Linguistics, 1977- (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - 01-100 Anthropology, 1976- (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - 01-120 III Sociology-Recon., 1979- (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - 01-160 Political Science, 1979- (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - 01-200 History Corner, 1979- (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - 01-240 German Studies, 1979- (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - 01-260 Language Corner, 1979- (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - 01-260 Engineering Corner 1960-76 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - 01-300 University Council, 1979- (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - 01-310 Building 310, 1979- (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - 01-320 Geology Corner, 1977- (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - 01-370 Physical Sciences, 1977- (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - 01-380 Sloan Mathematics Center (Math Corner), 1979- (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - 01-380 Sloan Mathematics Center (Air-Cond.) 1969- (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - 01-380 Computer Sci./Math. Sciences Statistics Renovation, 1979- (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - 01-420 Jordan Hall (Psychology), 1978- (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - 01-460 Margaret Jacks Hall, 1979- (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - 01-460 Margaret Jacks Hall, 1978- (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - 01-500 Memorial Church Organ 1977-78 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - 01-500 Memorial Church Organ, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - 01-500 Memorial Church, 1979- (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - 02-10 Bookstore 1976 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - 02-23 Center for Educational Research (CERAS), 1979 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - 02-50 Crown Law Quad, 1979- (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - 02-50 Crown Quadrangle Law School Fountain, 1979- (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - 02-60 Kresge Auditorium, 1978- (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - 02-100 Bowman Alumni House, 1978- (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - 02-120 Black House--418 Santa Teresa, 1978- (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - 02-130 Harmony House--561 Lomita Drive 1966- (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - 02-200 Music (Including Dinkelspiel), 1978- (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - 02-200 New Music Folder, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - 02-210 Braun (in design), 1979 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - 02-210 Braun (in design) 1978 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - 02-250 Institute for Energy Studies, 1978- (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - 02-250 PBX Telephone Building 1968- (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - 02-300 Tresidder Memorial Union, 1978- (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - 02-350 Faculty Club, 1979- (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - 02-400 Bechtel International Center, 1978- (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - 02-500 Terman Engineering Laboratory, 1978- (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - 02-520 Mechanical Engineering, 1979- (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - 02-530 Civil Engineering 1978 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - 02-540 Civil Engineering, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - 02-550 Peterson Laboratory, 1979- (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - 02-560 Reprographic Servies, 1979- (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - 02-570 High Temp Gas Dynamics, 1979- (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - 02-570 High Temp Gas Dynamics 1977-78 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - 02-580 Student Services Building (Old Union), 1979- (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - 02-590 Building 590 (including the Nitery), 1979 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - 02-600 Club House, 1979- (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - 02-610 Mechanical Engineering, 1979- (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - 02-620 Old Firehouse, 1978- (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - 02-630 Stanford University, 1979- (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - 02-650 Storke Student Publications Building, 1979- (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - 02-670 Butler Building (Mailing Services), 1979- (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - 02-914 Delta Upsilon--553 Mayfield, 1979- (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - 03-10 Cummings Art Building, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - 03-50 Career Planning and Placement Center, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - 03-55 Clock and Bell Tower, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - 03-100 Hoover Tower, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - 03-100 Hoover Tower Parking Lot "H", 1979- (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - 03-100 Hoover Fire Safety, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - 03-110 Lou Henry Hoover, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - 03-120 Herbert Hoover Memorial Building, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - 03-200 Green Library, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - 03-210/200 Green Library Budget, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - 03-200 Green Library Stacks, 1978- (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - 03-210 New Library, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - 03-400 Meyer Library, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - 03-400 Meyer Library Library Flood 1978 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - 04-50 Sequoia Hall, 1977- (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - 04-70 Center for Intergrated Systems, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - 04-150 Serra House, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - 04-200 Ginzton Laboratories, 1978- (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - 04-230 Applied Physics, 1978- (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - 04-230 Applied Physics, 1973- (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - 04-230 Via Pueblo Mail Development, 1978- (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - 04-230 Hubert Heffner Memorial Library, 1977- (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - 04-250 High Energy Physics Lab, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - 04-250 High Energy Physics Lab 1977 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - 04-300 Electronics Research Lab, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - 04-350 Applied Electronics Research Lab, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - 04-490 McCullough, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - 04-520 Varian Physics Lab, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - 04-520 Varian Physics Lab, 1977- (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - 04-540 Durand Building, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 30)